Kristian Colville

● Ireland 📞 +353833937493 🔟 kristiancolville96@gmail.com 🛊 GitHub 💄 LinkedIn 💾 Portfolio

Professional Profile

Currently completing a qualification with Code Institute since November 2021 in full-stack software development. A practical person with almost one year of experience using industry tools & technologies to build a portfolio of projects using a full-stack toolkit. Hard-working and achieving distinctions for the level of performance on the course. Core technical skills include HTML, CSS3, JavaScript, Python, Linux and Windows, and experience with Agile.

Skills

- Researching, Googling, documenting
- General IT
- ➤ Soft Skills
- ➤ UI/UX web design
- > Automated testing
- Version control Git
- Deployment testing Heroku

- > HTML, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Python
- Linux, Windows
- > Agile
- SQL PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- ➤ Software frameworks Django
- ➤ Full software development lifecycle

Education

2009 – 2014 CBS Thurles, Tipperary, Ireland	Irish Junior & Leaving Certificate (Highschool)
2020 – 2021 Archestown Thurles, Tipperary, Ireland	Microsoft Technology Associate
2021 – 2022 Code Institute, Dublin, Ireland	QQI Level 6 in Full-Stack Software Development

Certifications & Links

MTA: Operating System Fundamentals

MTA: Networking Fundamentals

MTA: Windows Server Administrating Fundamentals

MTA: Azure Fundamentals

Portfolio Projects & Links

★ Raza Noodles → HTML, CSS

★ Sudoku Master → HTML, CSS3, JavaScript

★ Rapid Silver → Python

★ Daily Sync → HTML, CSS3, JavaScript, Python (Django) (full-stack toolkit)

★ ECommerce website → Full-Stack toolkit (eCommerce web application)

(To be completed)

Employment History

05/2014 - 04/2016

AdTech

Assistant Technician

04/2016 - 02/2018

Tesco

Stock Control Clerk

02/2018 - 06/2019

Dew Valley Foods

- General Operative

01/2020 - 04/2021

Freelance

Computer Technician

10/2021 - 12/2021

Concentrix

- Information Technology Support Specialist

01/2022 - present

Freelance

- General Labour | IT | Software

rbin Culubb

Please visit my <u>LinkedIn page</u> to see duties. Various links at top of CV.

References

(Available on request)

Kind Regards,

Kristian Colville